[This drama is fictional and any similarity with reality is purely coincidental.]
[이 드라마는 허구이며 어떠한 유사성도 있습니다. 현실은 순전히 우연이다.]
[Production guidelines were followed when filming children and animals.]
[생산 지침을 따랐습니다. 어린이나 동물을 촬영할 때.]
[Episode 8]
[8화]
Hello.
안녕하세요.
- Hello. - You're here.
- 안녕하세요. - 여기 있어요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Welcome.
환영.
Taxi!
택시!
I'll explain later.
나중에 설명하겠습니다.
Please sit.
앉으세요.
You don't need to explain.
설명할 필요는 없습니다.
I'm sorry, but I wasn't informed about this blind date today.
죄송합니다만 알리지 못했습니다. 오늘 소개팅에 대해서요.
I said I'll explain everything.
내가 다 설명해주겠다고 했어.
Please, have a seat first.
먼저 자리에 앉으시기 바랍니다.
No, I think this happened because my mother doesn't know who I'm seeing.
아니, 내 생각엔 이런 일이 일어난 것 같아 우리 엄마는 내가 누구를 만나는지 모르셔요.
I apologize for what happened today.
오늘 일어난 일에 대해 사과드립니다.
Let's just pretend this never happened.
이런 일이 전혀 일어나지 않았다고 가정합시다.
Hey!
여기요!
Jang Hui Won?
장희원?
What? Why are you here, Hui Won?
무엇? 희원 씨, 왜 여기 있어요?
Well, I...
글쎄, 난...
Don't do this blind date.
이런 소개팅은 하지 마세요.
I like you.
좋아해요.
This is me.
나야.
Oh, that was quick.
아, 빨랐어요.
Indeed.
물론.
If you have any questions about the blind date...
질문이 있으시면 소개팅에 대해서..
You didn't know it was a blind date, and your mother arranged it on her own.
소개팅인 줄 몰랐을 텐데요. 그리고 네 엄마가 직접 준비하셨지.
I've almost memorized it.
거의 다 외웠어요.
It's late. You should go.
늦었어. 당신은 가야합니다.
Wow, seeing this place like this, it looks really beautiful.
와, 이런 곳을 보니, 정말 아름다워 보여요.
What time are you going to work tomorrow?
내일 몇 시에 출근할 예정인가요?
- Why do you ask? - I was thinking we could go together.
- 왜 물어보나요? - 같이 가면 어떨까 생각했어요.
Huh? We mustn't let it show at work. Okay?
뭐? 직장에서 그런 모습을 보여서는 안 됩니다. 좋아요?
I know that much.
나는 그 정도를 알고 있다.
But just in case.
하지만 혹시라도.
Shall we just take one more quick walk around here?
하나만 더 가져갈까 빨리 여기로 걸어갈래?
So we ended up walking two more laps.
그래서 우리는 두 바퀴를 더 걸었습니다.
You should go now.
지금 가세요.
We'll see each other at work anyway.
어쨌든 우리는 직장에서 다시 뵙겠습니다.
Got it.
알았어요.
But
하지만
is what you said earlier for real?
아까 말한 게 진짜야?
You know, all that stuff about being clingy and that we should go our separate ways.
알다시피 집착에 관한 모든 것 그리고 우리는 각자의 길을 가야 한다고.
I'm not sure if I really believe this.
내가 정말로 이것을 믿는지 잘 모르겠습니다.
I'm also worried you might change your mind again.
나도 걱정돼. 다시 마음을 바꾸세요.
It's a bit...
그것은 조금 ...
I mean, it's just...
내 말은, 그냥...
Ugh, whatever.
어, 뭐든지.
Wow, such a clear answer.
와, 정말 명쾌한 답변이네요.
Oh dear, oh dear.
아 이런, 아 이런.
What an embarrassment!
정말 당황스럽네요!
- Ms. Kim. - Yes.
- 김 선생님. - 예.
Did you know Du Jun is seeing someone?
두준이가 누군가를 만나고 있다는 걸 알고 있었나요?
Is the young master dating someone?
젊은 주인이 누군가와 데이트하고 있습니까?
I need to know if it's true or if he's just making excuses.
그것이 사실인지 알아야 해요 아니면 그가 단지 변명을 하고 있는 것인지.
And besides, that Mi Ran. I don't think she's the one I'm looking for.
게다가 그 미란. 내 생각엔 그 사람이 내가 찾고 있는 사람이 아닌 것 같아.
Her tone and voice are different, I'm sure.
그녀의 톤과 목소리는 확실히 다릅니다.
I should have seen her face back then somehow.
그 사람 얼굴을 봤어야 했는데 그때 어떻게든.
Anyway,
어쨌든,
please see
참조하세요
if you can find her.
그녀를 찾을 수 있다면.
Yes, understood.
네, 이해했습니다.
Oh dear.
이런.
Ugh, jeez.
으, 이런.
Ah, I'm being so foolish.
아, 내가 너무 바보같아.
Yes, hello?
응, 안녕?
Did you sleep well?
잘 주무셨나요?
Yes.
그렇습니다.
Did you sleep well, President?
잘 잤어요, 대통령님?
Yeah, I also slept well.
응, 나도 잘 잤어.
President, didn't you say
대통령님, 말씀하시지 않았나요
you usually can't sleep well because of insomnia or something?
너 평소에 잠을 잘 못 자잖아 불면증 때문인가?
That's right. I usually can't sleep well.
좋아요. 나는 평소에 잠을 잘 못 자요.
But thanks to someone, I slept like a baby.
그런데 누군가 덕분에 아기처럼 잤어요.
Not because of the blind date, right?
소개팅 때문은 아니겠죠?
Ah... well, I was pretty wiped out from it after all.
아... 뭐, 난 예뻤어 결국 그것에서 지워졌습니다.
What?
무엇?
Ah, I...
아, 난...
already miss you.
벌써 당신이 그리워요.
I kind of miss you too.
나도 당신이 좀 그리워요.
Today's Kang Du Jun.
오늘의 강두준.
What did you just say?
방금 뭐라고 했어?
Did you call me by my name?
내 이름으로 부르셨나요?
Say it again.
다시 말해보세요.
Huh? Say what?
뭐? 뭐라고?
You just said my name.
방금 내 이름을 말했잖아.
Just say it one more time.
한 번만 더 말씀해 주세요.
No.
아니요.
Why? It felt friendly and nice. Just once.
왜요? 친근하고 좋은 느낌이었습니다. 한 번만.
I'm hungry.
배고파요.
Aren't you hungry, President?
배고프지 않나요, 대통령님?
Why are you changing the subject?
왜 주제를 바꾸나요?
I usually don't eat breakfast.
나는 보통 아침을 먹지 않습니다.
But if someone asked me to eat together, I might gladly join.
하지만 누군가 나에게 묻는다면 함께 식사할 수 있다면 기꺼이 동참하겠습니다.
It's not like I'm saying we have to eat together right now.
내가 말하는 것과는 다르다 우리 지금 당장 같이 밥 먹어야 해.
Jang Hui Won, you know, you're really good at torturing people.
장희원 아시죠? 당신은 사람을 고문하는 데 정말 능숙해요.
Hope torture.
희망고문.
Well, I guess that's my charm.
뭐, 그게 제 매력인 것 같아요.
Jeez.
이런.
I'm in a rush and need to get ready.
나는 바쁘고 준비가 필요합니다.
We'll
우리는
have a meal together soon.
곧 함께 식사하세요.
I'll hang up now.
이제 전화를 끊겠습니다.
[Jang Hui Won]
[장희원]
We.
우리.
Right, 'we.'
그렇죠, '우리'죠.
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
- Oh, good morning. - Good morning.
- 아, 좋은 아침이에요. - 좋은 아침이에요.
Manager Jang, anything good happening lately?
장과장님 요즘 좋은 일 있으신가요?
Right, you're looking especially bright today.
그렇죠, 당신이 찾고 있는 거죠 오늘은 유난히 밝아.
Oh, this... it's just...
아, 이거... 그건 그냥...
- Just what? - What is it?
- 그냥 뭐요? - 그게 뭐죠?
Oh, well...
아, 글쎄...
It's a dress to cover my belly.
배를 가려주는 옷이에요.
I've gained some weight recently, you see.
최근에 살이 좀 쪘어요.
Just pretend you don't notice.
그냥 눈치채지 못한 척 하세요.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
- Sorry.
- 죄송합니다.
You look pretty today.
오늘 정말 예뻐 보이네요.
[Jang Hui Won] Makes me want to ask you out.
[장희원] 당신에게 데이트 신청을 하고 싶군요.
What?
무엇?
[President Kang Du Jun] Why don't you try kidnapping me then?
[강두준 회장] 그럼 나를 납치해 보는 게 어때요?
Secretary Go, please set your phone to vibrate in public places.
고비서님, 전화기 좀 바꿔주세요 공공장소에서 진동을 주기 위해
Ah, just a moment.
아, 잠시만요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
If you're going to apologize, do it properly, okay?
사과할 생각이라면, 제대로 해, 알았지?
Ugh.
윽.
- Now. - What's now?
- 지금. - 지금은 뭐예요?
- What? - What is it?
- 무엇? - 그게 뭐죠?
Now's the perfect time to have a snack before lunch.
지금이 딱 좋은 때야 점심 식사 전에 간식을 먹으려고.
- So it's now. - Manager.
- 이제 됐네요. - 관리자.
Do you still feel bitter about not getting any snacks?
아직도 씁쓸한 마음이 드시나요? 간식은 안 먹어?
You ate all the madeleines Se Hyeon brought from France last time,
마들렌을 다 먹었구나 세현아 저번에 프랑스에서 가져온
and I didn't get any.
그리고 나는 아무것도 얻지 못했습니다.
- Me neither. - What a shame.
- 나도 마찬가지야. - 정말 안타깝네요.
- But the two of us ate them. - We did?
- 그런데 둘이서 먹었어요. - 우리가 그랬나요?
- It's because of his three kids. - You didn't get any back then?
- 세 아이 때문이에요. - 그땐 아무것도 못 받았나요?
What?
무엇?
I'll bring something more delicious for everyone next time, except Manager Nah.
더 맛있는거 가져올게요 다음에는 나 매니저 빼고 모두에게.
Fine, I'll go on a trip too and buy for everyone except Se Hyeon.
알았어 나도 여행갈게 그리고 세현 빼고 다 사줘.
Oh, my.
아, 이런.
Team Leader!
팀 리더!
To boost work efficiency, how about a snack break?
업무 효율성을 높이기 위해, 간식 먹는 건 어때?
In my opinion, work efficiency would skyrocket if you would just stop talking.
제 생각에는 업무 효율성이 말을 멈추면 급등합니다.
Everyone, dismissed!
모두 해고!
The snack delivery is here!
간식배달이 왔습니다!
Oh my goodness.
아, 맙소사.
It seemed like the perfect snack time.
완벽한 간식 시간 같았습니다.
As expected of our president!
역시 우리 대통령님!
President, I respect and love you.
대통령님, 존경하고 사랑합니다.
How did you even think to get snacks for us too?
어떻게 생각한 거야? 우리도 간식 사줄까?
Because it's pretty.
왜냐면 예쁘거든요.
The desserts looked so pretty,
디저트가 너무 예뻐보였는데,
so I thought it'd be nice if we all shared them.
그래서 좋을 줄 알았는데 우리 모두가 그것을 공유한다면.
They say beautiful things taste good too, and this is completely delicious.
아름다운 것은 맛도 좋다고 하던데, 와 이거 완전 맛있어요.
I know, it's completely sweet and refreshing.
알아요, 완전 달콤하고 상큼해요.
I wonder who they're for?
누구를 위한 것인지 궁금합니다.
Here, have some drinks too.
여기도 한잔 하세요.
We have a meeting, so we'll head out first.
우리는 회의가 있어서 먼저 나가겠습니다.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
- 즐기다. - 감사합니다.
I made it super tangy, with lots of ice.
얼음을 많이 넣어서 아주 톡 쏘는 맛으로 만들었어요.
- Secretary Go. - Oh, jeez.
- 고 비서. - 아, 이런.
- Oh, that startled me.
- 아, 깜짝 놀랐어요.
Yes, I'm going.
네, 갈 거예요.
Ah, then I'll take my leave too.
아, 그럼 나도 이만 갈게.
Yes.
예.
[I Love U]
[사랑해요]
Team Leader, you said you weren't going to have any snacks?
팀장님은 아니라고 하셨습니다 간식 먹을래?
Oh, I have to try this one.
아 이거 해봐야겠네요.
It's really tasty.
정말 맛있어요.
I don't know why I get so tired after just eating lunch.
왜 받는지 모르겠어요 방금 점심을 먹고 나니까 너무 피곤해요.
It's a food coma, total food coma.
음식물 혼수상태, 완전 음식물 혼수상태입니다.
- Yeah. - Want to grab coffee?
- 응. - 커피 마실래?
Sure, where to?
물론이죠. 어디로 갈까요?
That cafe you mentioned back then.
그때 네가 말했던 그 카페.
- Cute! - Let's try it.
- 귀여운! - 한번 해보자.
That cafe in front of the company you mentioned.
바로 앞에 있는 저 카페 당신이 언급한 회사.
Then let's go to the cafe in front of that company.
그럼 카페로 가자 그 회사 앞이에요.
Manager.
관리자.
- Huh? - Are you hot?
- 뭐? - 더워요?
Right, why is your face so red?
그렇죠, 얼굴이 왜 이렇게 빨개요?
Oh.
오.
It suddenly got hot.
갑자기 더워졌습니다.
Aren't you feeling hot?
몸이 덥지 않나요?
Am I the only one feeling this hot?
나만 이렇게 더워지는 걸까?
Assistant Manager, are you hot?
대리님, 화났나요?
I'm cold.
나는 추워요.
- What?
- 무엇?
What?
무엇?
So you do all kinds of things, huh?
그럼 별 짓 다 하네, 응?
Darn it, stop copying me.
젠장, 그만 따라하세요.
What did you say? What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요? 뭐라고 하셨나요?
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Oh dear.
이런.
You're making such a scene just to show it off. Totally losing it, huh?
이런 장면을 만들고 있구나 그냥 자랑하려고요. 완전히 졌죠?
Did it show?
보여줬나요?
Yeah, totally.
응, 완전.
Why are you just openly walking around like it's Day 1 of dating?
왜 대놓고 돌아다녀? 마치 데이트 첫날인 것 같죠?
Hui Won said we absolutely shouldn't let it show.
희원이는 우리는 절대라고 했어 보여주면 안 된다.
But if even her yawns are that cute, what am I supposed to do?
하지만 하품마저도 그렇게 귀여우면 내가 뭘 해야 하지?
What are you supposed to do?
당신은 무엇을 해야 합니까?
But she did look tired.
하지만 그녀는 피곤해 보였습니다.
Si Hyeong, aren't you tired?
시형아, 피곤하지 않니?
No, I'm not tired.
아니요, 피곤하지 않아요.
All of this is because I've been keeping myself in shape.
이 모든 것은 나는 몸매를 유지하고 있습니다.
No, you must be tired, Si Hyeong.
아니, 시형씨 피곤하겠어요.
Especially after going out to buy dessert earlier.
특히 외출 후 디저트를 더 일찍 사려고
I drove, so I'm not tired at all.
운전해서 그런지 전혀 피곤하지 않아요.
No, Si Hyeong, you're clearly exhausted right now.
아니 시형아 넌 분명해 지금은 지쳤어.
Look at your face, dark circles and dull skin.
얼굴 좀 보세요, 다크서클과 칙칙한 피부.
- You didn't sleep last night, did you? - No.
- 어젯밤에 잠을 못 잤죠? - 아니.
I said I'm not tired.
나는 피곤하지 않다고 말했다.
No.
아니요.
You're exactly in need of a break right now.
당신은 지금 당장 휴식이 필요합니다.
We have an urgent announcement.
긴급 공지사항이 있습니다.
For the next two hours, to help our staff recharge,
앞으로 2시간 동안 직원들의 재충전을 돕기 위해
the President has initiated nap time...
대통령이 낮잠 시간을 시작했습니다...
Nap time?
낮잠 시간?
This is the first time, right?
이번이 처음이죠?
So, does that mean every employee is being forced to rest for two hours?
그렇다면 그것은 모든 직원을 의미하는가? 두 시간 동안 강제로 쉬어야 한다고?
More than forced, isn't it considerate?
강요라기보다 배려가 아닐까요?
Wow, as expected of our president.
와, 역시 우리 대통령님이시군요.
The perks are amazing.
특혜는 놀랍습니다.
No more yawning in front of colleagues.
더 이상 동료들 앞에서 하품을 하지 않습니다.
It's way too dangerously charming.
너무 위험할 정도로 매력적이에요.
What? Is he allowed to do this?
무엇? 그 사람이 이런 일을 해도 됩니까?
Oh, jeez.
아, 이런.
What?
무엇?
Is that your boyfriend?
그 사람이 당신 남자친구인가요?
Pardon?
뭐라고요?
Why are you so happy?
왜 그렇게 행복해요?
Manager, do you have a boyfriend?
매니저님, 남자친구 있어요?
What, you didn't even tell us?
뭐야, 우리한테도 말하지 않았어?
What boyfriend? He's just a friend.
무슨 남자 친구? 그는 단지 친구입니다.
I mean, when would I have time to date?
내 말은, 언제 데이트할 시간이 있겠어?
True, she's always all about work.
사실, 그녀는 항상 일에만 전념합니다.
When would she even have time to see a guy?
그녀는 언제 남자를 만날 시간이 있을까요?
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
Exactly, I'm working even now.
정확히는 지금도 일하고 ​​있어요.
Se Hyeon.
세현.
Can you send me the file you were supposed to send?
파일을 보내주실 수 있나요? 보내기로 했잖아?
Yes.
예.
Manager, could it be that she really has a boyfriend?
매니저님, 그럴까요? 그 사람 정말 남자친구 있어요?
Right?
오른쪽?
Manager Jang does seem different today.
장과장님은 오늘따라 달라보이시네요.
I totally get the vibe of being in love.
나는 완전히 사랑에 빠진 분위기를 느낍니다.
No, really. Why is everyone suddenly so interested in me today?
아뇨, 정말요. 다들 왜? 오늘 갑자기 나한테 그렇게 관심이 많아?
I really don't have a boyfriend.
저는 정말 남자친구가 없어요.
So drop this now.
그러니 지금 이것을 버리십시오.
Come on, if you have one, just tell us.
자, 갖고 계시다면 말씀해 주세요.
Your skin looks different though?
그런데 피부가 좀 달라진 것 같죠?
Don't tell me yesterday...
어제 말하지 마세요...
- It changed? - Yeah.
- 달라졌나요? - 응.
Jeez.
이런.
Manager.
관리자.
Here for the contest meeting?
대회 회의를 위해 여기로 오셨나요?
Isn't that scheduled for the afternoon?
오후로 예정되어 있지 않나요?
No.
아니요.
Ah, yes, correct.
아, 네, 맞습니다.
- But... - So you came to see Manager Jang?
- 하지만... - 그럼 장과장님을 만나러 오셨나요?
I'll call Manager Jang for you.
제가 장과장님한테 전화할게요.
No need.
필요하지 않습니다.
I just told you...
방금 말했잖아...
Oh, I didn't come to see Hui Won.
아, 저는 희원을 만나러 온 것이 아닙니다.
Ah, the meeting is this afternoon.
아, 회의가 오늘 오후에요.
That should be in the group chat notice.
그건 그룹채팅 공지에 있을 거에요.
I'll double-check and then...
다시 한 번 확인해보고 나서...
Yeah? Then I'll tell Manager Jang.
응? 그럼 장과장님께 말씀드리겠다.
- No. - Fine, go ahead.
- 아니. - 좋아요, 계속하세요.
- I'll go ahead. - Yeah.
- 내가 먼저 갈게. - 응.
Manager, I'll confirm it and come back this afternoon.
매니저님, 확인하겠습니다 그리고 오늘 오후에 다시 오세요.
Sure, Assistant Manager Cha.
물론이죠, 차 대리님.
- Take care. - Yes.
- 잘 지내세요. - 예.
President, on the office floor,
회장님, 사무실 바닥에서
Mr. Lee is here.
이씨가 왔습니다.
Who?
WHO?
How dare he come here?
그 사람이 어떻게 감히 여기에 올 수가 있어?
Then I'll send him back.
그러면 내가 그 사람을 돌려보내겠습니다.
No, send him in.
아니요, 그를 안으로 보내세요.
Yes.
그렇습니다.
I've committed an unforgivable sin.
나는 용서받을 수 없는 죄를 지었습니다.
Please forgive me just this once.
이번 한 번만 용서해주세요.
How predictable.
얼마나 예측 가능한가.
If you betrayed me for this, I'm disappointed.
이 때문에 나를 배신했다면, 나는 실망했다.
I'll do anything.
나는 무엇이든 할 것이다.
If you just let me redo the sculpture...
조각품을 다시 만들게 해주시면...
A dog that bites its owner
주인을 무는 개
will bite again when cornered.
코너링되면 다시 물릴 것입니다.
Why should I give
왜 주어야 하나?
someone like you another chance?
너 같은 사람한테 또 기회가 있겠어?
A dog only does what it's told, doesn't it?
개는 시키는 대로만 행동하지 않나요?
I'll prove I'm more than that.
나는 그 이상임을 증명할 것이다.
Now you sound like an artist. Interesting.
이제 당신은 예술가처럼 들립니다. 흥미로운.
Wait for my call.
내 전화를 기다리세요.
Go take a bath.
가서 목욕하세요.
Is it really right to keep going with this?
정말 이 일을 계속하는 것이 맞는 걸까요?
Manager Jang.
장 매니저님.
About next year's new product line...
내년 신제품 라인에 대해…
Manager.
매니저.
- What? - Do you happen to have
- 무엇? - 혹시 그런 적이 있나요?
the file that summarizes the new product lineup for the first half of next year?
신제품을 요약한 파일 내년 상반기 라인업은?
The team leader is looking for it, but I haven't...
팀장이 찾고 있는데, 하지만 난 안 그랬어...
- finished organizing it yet. - Oh, that one?
- 아직 정리가 다 끝났어요. - 아, 그거요?
One moment.
잠시만요.
Here, this one.
여기, 이거요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Is something bothering you?
뭔가 괴로운 일이 있나요?
You've been sighing nonstop since earlier.
당신은 아까부터 쉬지 않고 한숨을 쉬었습니다.
I'm just worried whether non-alcoholic beer has real commercialization potential.
그냥 무알콜 맥주인지 걱정이 되네요 실제 상용화 가능성이 있습니다.
Oh, because of the contest?
아, 대회 때문에요?
It is challenging.
그것은 도전적이다.
Since it's non-alcoholic, it's hard to be sure there'll be enough demand.
무알콜이라 힘들어요 수요가 충분할 것이라고 확신합니다.
So I'm seriously wondering if I should switch to a different idea.
그래서 진지하게 궁금해지는데 다른 아이디어로 전환해야 한다면.
But I tend to trust your instincts.
하지만 나는 당신의 직감을 신뢰하는 경향이 있습니다.
- Pardon? - Everything you've planned so far
- 뭐라고요? - 지금까지 계획한 모든 것
has been good.
좋은되었습니다.
I think good products usually start with wanting to solve
평소에는 좋은 제품이라고 생각하는데 해결하고 싶은 것부터 시작하라
someone's inconvenience.
누군가의 불편함.
Like the Try Golden Ratio Glass.
황금비율 유리를 사용해 보세요.
It was made for people who struggle with mixing ratios.
사람들을 위해 만들어졌죠 혼합 비율에 어려움을 겪는 사람.
Right.
오른쪽.
- Wasn't it? - And besides,
- 그렇지 않았나요? - 게다가,
isn't it your style to just go for it first?
그냥 먼저 가보는 스타일 아닌가요?
Assistant Manager Choi.
최 대리.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I really appreciate it too.
저도 정말 감사해요.
The idea of wanting to solve an inconvenience,
해결하고 싶다는 생각 불편함,
and a beer people can enjoy together in a healthy way.
사람들이 즐길 수 있는 맥주 건강하게 함께해요.
Huh? Non-alcoholic?
뭐? 무알콜?
So you're going for non-alcoholic beer for the contest?
그래서 당신은 갈거야 대회에 무알콜 맥주?
Manager Nah's high-proof beer
나점장의 하이프루프 맥주
versus Manager Jang's non-alcoholic beer.
장과장의 무알콜 맥주.
You two are on total opposite ends of the spectrum.
너희 둘은 완전 스펙트럼의 반대쪽 끝.
Don't you know non-alcoholic has limited market potential?
무알콜을 모르시나요? 시장 잠재력이 제한되어 있나요?
Marketability is part of the judging criteria.
시장성은 일부 심사기준 중.
The global non-alcoholic beer market
세계의 무알콜 맥주 시장
is growing 8 to 10% annually.
매년 8~10%씩 성장하고 있다.
Now's the chance to capture the emerging market early.
지금이 잡을 기회다 신흥시장을 조기에
Come on, why drink if you don't want to get drunk?
자, 술을 왜 마셔? 취하고 싶지 않아?
Come on, so many young people prioritize health nowadays.
자, 젊은 사람들이 너무 많아 요즘은 건강이 우선이다.
Thinking people drink just to get drunk is such an old-school mindset.
사람들은 단지 취하려고 술을 마신다고 생각한다 정말 구식 사고 방식입니다.
- Old-school. - Among American youth,
- 옛날식. - 미국 청소년 중에는
they say sober curious has become a real social phenomenon.
사람들은 진지한 호기심이 생겼다고 해요 진짜 사회현상.
The culture of enjoying alcohol without getting drunk is growing...
술을 즐기는 문화 취하지 않고 자라는 중..
Sober Mercury or whatever, I'm against it.
냉정한 머큐리든 뭐든, 나는 그것에 반대합니다.
Go ask around college campuses.
대학 캠퍼스에 가서 물어보세요.
Who prefers non-alcoholic over high-proof?
누가 도수 높은 알코올보다 무알콜 알코올을 선호합니까?
Right, Assistant Manager Cha?
그렇지, 차대리?
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
Well,
글쎄,
from selling to various stores,
판매부터 다양한 매장까지,
both feasibility and marketability
타당성과 시장성을 모두 갖춘
are far superior for high-proof beer.
도수가 높은 맥주에 비해 훨씬 뛰어납니다.
See?
보다?
But if we were just going to go with familiar, safe ideas,
하지만 우리가 그냥 가려고 했다면 익숙하고 안전한 아이디어로
I don't think they'd bother holding a contest like this.
내 생각엔 그 사람들이 귀찮게 할 것 같지 않아 이런 콘테스트를 개최합니다.
The whole point is innovation and fresh ideas,
요점은 혁신과 신선한 아이디어,
so this is when we need a differentiated perspective.
그러니 지금이 우리에게 필요할 때야 차별화된 관점.
No, innovation doesn't mean unprofitable ideas.
아니요, 혁신은 그렇지 않습니다. 수익성 없는 아이디어를 의미합니다.
We won't know profitability until we try.
시도하기 전에는 수익성을 알 수 없습니다.
I'll do market research by next week.
다음 주까지 시장 조사를 할게요.
All I need to do is prove
내가 해야 할 일은 증명하는 것뿐이다
whether non-alcoholic beer will resonate
무알콜 맥주가 울릴지 여부
with young people or not, right?
젊은이들과 함께 있든 없든, 그렇죠?
Would that be okay?
괜찮을까요?
I'm on your side, Manager, but my friends might think differently, so...
나는 매니저님 편이지만 내 친구들은 다르게 생각할 수도 있으니...
Then that's exactly what we need.
그렇다면 바로 이것이 우리에게 필요한 것입니다.
Pardon?
뭐라고요?
Manager Nah has a point.
나 감독의 말이 일리가 있다.
I acknowledge that somewhat.
그 점은 어느 정도 인정합니다.
I've always heard 'it's impossible,' now I'll show it works.
'불가능하다'는 말을 늘 들어왔지만 이제 작동하는 모습을 보여드리겠습니다.
The real question for me is
나에게 진짜 질문은
what kind of non-alcoholic beer
무알콜 맥주는 어떤 종류인가요?
could actually change the market.
실제로 시장을 변화시킬 수 있습니다.
Oh, Manager.
아, 매니저님.
Um, would you mind heading in first?
음, 먼저 들어가시겠어요?
I need to talk with Assistant Manager Cha.
차 대리와 얘기 좀 해야 해요.
Oh, sure.
아, 물론이죠.
Well, shall we talk for a moment?
자, 잠시 얘기 좀 해볼까요?
I have something to tell you.
당신에게 할 말이 있습니다.
Can I go first?
나 먼저 가도 될까?
Have you talked with the President? About the blind date.
대통령과 통화해보셨나요? 소개팅에 대해서.
Why are you looking at me like that?
왜 나를 그렇게 보는 거죠?
Min Uk, you're so thoughtful.
민욱 씨, 정말 사려 깊으세요.
You're always kind to me.
당신은 항상 나에게 친절합니다.
What's that mean? Of course I'd...
그게 무슨 뜻이에요? 물론 난...
It's not a given.
그것은 주어진 것이 아닙니다.
Putting others before yourself is incredibly hard.
자신보다 다른 사람을 먼저 생각하기 엄청나게 어렵습니다.
I think
내 생각엔
that might be why I liked you.
그래서 내가 당신을 좋아했을 수도 있어요.
Huh?
뭐?
But thinking back,
그런데 다시 생각해 보면,
I confused gratitude with romantic feelings.
나는 감사와 낭만적인 감정을 혼동했습니다.
Actually,
실제로,
I went to his blind date.
나는 그의 소개팅에 갔다.
You went there?
거기 갔었어?
There was a misunderstanding.
오해가 있었습니다.
Before your call,
전화하기 전에,
I wasn't sure about my feelings.
나는 내 감정에 대해 확신이 없었습니다.
But once I heard about the blind date, that's when I realized it.
그런데 소개팅 얘기를 듣자마자 그때 나는 그것을 깨달았습니다.
I like the President.
나는 대통령을 좋아한다.
Sorry, I can't give the answer you want.
죄송합니다. 원하시는 답변을 드릴 수 없습니다.
- I knew it. - Huh?
- 그럴 줄 알았어. - 뭐?
I've known you for years.
나는 당신을 수년간 알고 지냈어요.
I didn't confess to you without being prepared for this much.
나는 당신에게 고백하지 않았다 이만큼은 준비하지 않고.
And I don't think this is over yet.
그리고 나는 이것이 아직 끝나지 않았다고 생각합니다.
- Min Uk. - I want to see this through.
- 민욱. - 나는 이것을 끝까지 보고 싶다.
So please don't cut it off so decisively.
그러니 너무 단호하게 끊어내지 마시기 바랍니다.
I'll go ahead.
나는 계속할 것이다.
Oh.
오.
It seems you basically handles all the work around here.
당신이 기본적으로 처리하는 것 같습니다 여기 주변의 모든 일이요.
President.
대통령.
Why? Is something wrong?
왜? 뭔가 문제가 있나요?
You don't look well.
당신은 표정이 좋지 않습니다.
No, it's just that I have a lot on my plate, and my belly keeps growing.
아니, 그냥 내 접시에 양이 너무 많아서 그리고 내 배는 계속 커지고 있어요.
I'm starting to feel a bit pressed.
조금 압박감을 느끼기 시작했어요.
Even when handing things over,
물건을 넘겨줄 때도
I want to make it easy for the next person to follow.
쉽게 만들고 싶어 다음 사람이 따라갈 수 있도록.
- That's cool. - Huh?
- 멋지네요. - 뭐?
I mean, you are cool.
내 말은, 당신은 멋지다.
Your passion for work, and the way you think about your coworkers.
일에 대한 열정과 방식 당신은 동료에 대해 생각합니다.
Wait, you just realized that now?
잠깐, 이제야 그걸 깨달았나요?
I guess so.
그런 것 같아요.
If I wanted to know more, what should I do?
더 알고 싶으면 어떻게 해야 하나요?
What? Is someone there?
무엇? 거기 누군가 있나요?
There shouldn't be anyone here.
여기에는 아무도 없어야 합니다.
Quick, hide!
빨리, 숨어!
Over there, over there.
저기, 저기.
But if any employee is here at this hour... There shouldn't be anyone.
그런데 이 시간에 직원이 있다면... 누구도 있어서는 안 됩니다.
Don't worry. I've confirmed everyone left.
괜찮아요. 모두가 떠난 것을 확인했습니다.
Then, would you like to eat in my office?
그럼 내 사무실에서 식사할래?
Shall we?
우리 할까요?
Team Leader Bang and Secretary Go?
방 팀장과 고 비서?
Hold on.
기다리다.
What's this smell? Smells delicious.
이 냄새는 무엇입니까? 맛있는 냄새가 난다.
What smell could it be?
무슨 냄새일까요?
It's the smell of my heart burning.
내 마음이 타는 냄새입니다.
I'm hungry. Let's go in and eat.
배고파요. 들어가서 먹자.
Noona.
누나.
Oh, noona.
아, 누나.
So he's dating Team Leader Bang? Just the two of them?
그럼 방팀장이랑 사귄다는 건가요? 둘만?
He's finally gone crazy.
그는 마침내 미쳐버렸습니다.
Oh my, oh my.
이런, 이런.
It's now. Get out quickly.
지금이다. 빨리 나가세요.
Seriously...
진심으로...
[Requesting a driver within 12 minutes]
[12분 이내 운전기사 요청]
No taxis around.
주변에 택시가 없습니다.
I can't get one on the app either.
앱에서도 받을 수 없습니다.
I should've just gone to get the car keys.
그냥 차 열쇠 가지러 갔어야 했는데.
Even so, they seem to be on a date. Let's not get in the way.
그럼에도 불구하고 그들은 데이트 중인 것 같습니다. 방해하지 말자.
Jeez.
이런.
Still, if you catch a cold...
그래도 감기 걸리면..
This won't do. I'll just call Secretary Go to bring the car now.
이건 안 돼요. 그냥 전화할게 비서 지금 차를 가져오러 가세요.
No, please don't.
아니요, 그러지 마세요.
Oh, a taxi's here.
아, 택시가 왔어요.
- Get in. - Should I go?
- 들어가세요. - 갈까?
I still have work to finish.
아직 끝내야 할 일이 남아 있어요.
Please make sure she gets home safely.
그녀가 집에 안전하게 도착할 수 있도록 해주세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
- President. - Call me when you get home.
- 대통령. - 집에 오면 전화해.
President, wait.
대통령님, 잠깐만요.
- I'll call Secretary Go to bring the car. - No, please don't.
- 고 비서에게 전화해서 차를 가져오겠습니다. - 아니, 그러지 마세요.
Am I being too sensitive?
내가 너무 예민한 걸까?
Ugh.
윽.
Of all people, a blind date with the Taehan Liquor President?
모든 사람들의 소개팅 대한주류 사장이랑?
Does Hui Won know about this too?
희원씨도 이 사실을 알고 있나요?
Should I tell her, or not?
그녀에게 말해야 할까, 말까?
Huh?
뭐?
- Jang Hui Won. - What?
- 장희원. - 무엇?
Why are you here, Hui Won?
희원 씨, 왜 여기 있어요?
What? She knew everything already.
무엇? 그녀는 이미 모든 것을 알고 있었습니다.
Does Min Uk know?
민욱이는 알까?
[Hangover Remedy] Jeez.
[숙취해소제] 이런.
I'm in no position to worry about anyone.
나는 누구에게도 걱정할 입장이 아니다.
Honestly, I regretted it the whole way home.
솔직히 집에 오는 내내 후회했어요.
I shouldn't have stepped aside.
나는 옆으로 물러나지 말았어야 했다.
Is something wrong?
뭔가 문제가 있나요?
You've been acting strange lately.
요즘 당신이 이상하게 행동했어요.
You keep acting childish while competing with the President.
계속 유치하게 굴잖아 대통령과 경쟁하면서.
Even had a pride contest over drinks.
술을 놓고 자존심 대결도 벌였습니다.
Do you really not know why I'm like this?
내가 왜 이러는지 정말 모르시나요?
Did she dump you?
그 사람이 당신을 버렸나요?
You reminded me of myself, the way I used to drink after I broke up.
넌 나 자신을 생각나게 했어, 길 헤어진 후에 술을 마시곤 했어요.
- Why are you here? - The owner called me.
- 왜 여기 있어요? - 주인이 전화했어요.
She said my friend is here, moping alone.
내 친구가 여기 혼자 청소하고 있다고 하더군요.
Just kidding. She told me to come take care of you.
농담이에요. 그녀는 나에게 말했다 당신을 돌보러 오세요.
She asked why the three of us haven't been hanging out lately.
그녀는 왜 우리 셋이냐고 물었어 최근에 같이 놀지 않았어.
Are you disappointed it's not Hui Won?
희원이 아니라서 실망했나요?
It's not that.
그게 아닙니다.
I just feel like I had so many chances, and I let them all slip away.
그냥 기회가 너무 많았던 것 같아요. 그리고 나는 그들 모두가 빠져나가도록 내버려두었습니다.
I thought courage was only needed to confess your feelings.
용기만이 유일한 줄 알았는데 자신의 감정을 고백해야 합니다.
But it turns out,
그러나 그것은 밝혀졌습니다.
being rejected takes courage too.
거절당하는 것에도 용기가 필요하다.
You're amazing, Hwang Mi Ran.
넌 정말 대단해, ​​황미란.
You're much braver than I am.
당신은 나보다 훨씬 용감해요.
You just realized that now?
이제야 깨달았나요?
Maybe I'm just being stupidly naive.
어쩌면 나는 단지 어리석게 순진한 것일 수도 있습니다.
Why did I even come back here?
내가 왜 여기로 돌아왔을까?
I know you're naive.
당신이 순진한 거 알아요.
- What? - I mean, why did you come here?
- 무엇? - 내 말은, 왜 여기에 왔나요?
What did you expect to see?
무엇을 기대했나요?
I came to see you all disheveled like a mess.
엉망진창처럼 흐트러진 모습으로 여러분을 만나러 왔습니다.
Did you come for revenge?
복수하러 오셨나요?
Yeah, but don't get me wrong.
응, 하지만 오해하진 마.
Today, I'm not Hwang Mi Ran who likes you.
오늘 나는 너를 좋아하는 황미란이 아니다.
I came as your friend Hwang Mi Ran.
나는 너의 친구 황미란으로 왔다.
Just for today, as a friend, I'll listen to everything.
오늘만은 친구로서 내가 다 들어줄게.
Just like you always did for me.
당신이 나에게 늘 그랬던 것처럼요.
So don't drink alone.
그러니 혼자 술을 마시지 마세요.
I'm upset.
나는 속상하다.
Seriously, did I just send a pregnant woman off in a taxi?
진짜야, 내가 방금 보낸 거야? 임산부가 택시를 탔다?
And why did I pull my hand away there?
그리고 나는 왜 거기에서 손을 빼냈는가?
Jeez.
이런.
She must be so disappointed.
그녀는 정말 실망했을 것입니다.
I should've taken her home, or at least shared the taxi with her.
그녀를 집에 데려갔어야 했는데, 아니면 적어도 그녀와 택시를 공유했습니다.
Jeez.
이런.
She hasn't even contacted me.
그녀는 나에게 연락조차 하지 않았습니다.
I wonder if she got home safely.
그녀가 집에 무사히 도착했는지 궁금해요.
She couldn't be sulking, could she?
그녀는 부루퉁할 리가 없지 않습니까?
Ugh, after leaving like that, I'd be upset too if I were her.
윽, 그렇게 떠나고 나면 내가 그 사람이었다면 나도 속상했을 것이다.
Well, I can make it up to her.
글쎄요, 제가 그 사람에게 보상해드릴 수 있어요.
Finding great restaurants and planning date routes is my specialty.
훌륭한 레스토랑 찾기 데이트 코스를 계획하는 것이 내 전문 분야입니다.
Cultural stuff, performances, exhibitions, then a date that flows smoothly
문화재, 공연, 전시, 그럼 순조롭게 흘러가는 데이트
into a nearby restaurant, a cafe, and a walking path.
근처 식당으로 들어가, 카페와 산책로.
If she wants something more active,
그녀가 좀 더 활동적인 것을 원한다면,
[A park or near the Han River] head to an open park or near the Han River,
[공원 또는 한강 주변] 탁 트인 공원이나 한강 근처로 가보세요.
hop on a bike, and just ride.
자전거를 타고 그냥 타세요.
The view's nice. Take pictures there.
전망이 좋아요. 거기에서 사진을 찍으세요.
Ah, but Hui Won might not be up for that.
아, 하지만 희원은 그럴 마음이 없을 수도 있다.
Well, then.
그럼요.
Oh! A food-focused date.
오! 음식 중심의 데이트.
[A foodie date] How about a foodie date?
[식도락 데이트] 미식가 데이트 어때요?
Ah, no.
아, 아니.
You know, something women love.
아시다시피 여자들이 좋아하는 게 있죠.
[Shopping] Shopping. Yeah, shopping.
[쇼핑] 쇼핑. 응, 쇼핑.
Starting light with shopping isn't a bad idea either. Yeah, that should work.
쇼핑으로 가볍게 시작하는 것은 아니다 그것도 나쁜 생각이야. 네, 그럴 거예요.
Your answers just flow out like rap.
너의 대답은 랩처럼 흘러나온다.
I told you, it's my specialty.
내가 말했잖아, 그건 내 전문이야.
So which one do you like best?
그럼 어느 것이 가장 마음에 드나요?
Let's go on a date today.
오늘 데이트하자.
I'll come pick you up at your place by eleven.
내가 데리러 갈게 11시까지 네 집에 와.
This one looks like it might be tight around the waist too.
이건 그럴 수도 있을 것 같네요 허리 둘레도 꽉 조여요.
When did this get so small?
언제 이렇게 작아졌지?
Do I need to start buying maternity clothes soon?
구매를 시작해야 합니까? 곧 출산복?
Let's go.
갑시다.
Yes.
예.
These are our new arrivals.
저희 새로 도착한 분들입니다.
I've got several laid out, so pick one.
여러개 준비되어 있으니 하나 골라보세요.
This one and this one.
이것과 이것.
- This one and... - Pick a few more.
- 이것과... - 몇 가지 더 골라보세요.
The pink one.
핑크색.
- This one is really pretty. - Jeez.
- 이거 정말 예쁘네요. - 이런.
Right? Isn't she pretty?
오른쪽? 그녀는 예쁘지 않나요?
Please don't.
그러지 마세요.
Huh? It's been a while.
뭐? 오랜만이에요.
- Brother-in-law? - What, brother-in-law?
- 처남? - 뭐, 형님?
Then you and President are...
그렇다면 당신과 대통령은...
You two know each other?
둘이 아는 사이야?
Ah, we ran into each other at my regular spot.
아, 우연히 마주쳤어 내 단골 자리에.
By chance?
우연히?
Secretary Yoon.
윤 비서.
So the person you are seeing
그럼 지금 만나고 있는 사람은
is Hui Won?
휘원이야?
Oh my, are we going to be family soon?
아, 우리 이제 곧 가족이 되는 건가요?
Well then, why not just come and greet the family?
그럼 그냥 하면 안되는 이유 와서 가족들에게 인사할까?
Mother and Father,
어머니와 아버지,
if they hear you are the person he is marrying, they'd be delighted.
그들이 듣는다면 당신은 그 사람입니다 그가 결혼한다면 그들은 기뻐할 거예요.
We'll handle that ourselves.
우리가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
Why, if she's a woman you brought,
왜, 당신이 데려온 여자라면,
even my late husband would have liked her.
죽은 남편도 그녀를 좋아했을 거예요.
Oh, can you actually hold hands now?
아, 이제 실제로 손을 잡을 수 있나요?
Jeong Eum.
정음.
Stop this.
그만둬.
We'll head out first.
우리 먼저 나가겠습니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Does he even realize his wallet's missing?
그 사람은 지갑이 없어진 걸 깨닫는 걸까요?
Not a single call, and making me wait all the time.
전화 한통도 안하고 나를 이렇게 만드는구나 항상 기다리십시오.
Oh, Dad.
아, 아빠.
You're getting off work soon, right?
이제 곧 퇴근하는 거 맞죠?
Yeah, a little later.
응, 조금 이따.
Did you call to ask about that?
그거 물어보려고 전화했어요?
Oh no, that's not it.
아뇨, 그게 아닙니다.
Hey, are you free tomorrow?
저기, 내일 시간 있어요?
Huh? What is it? This feels really familiar.
뭐? 그것은 무엇입니까? 정말 익숙한 느낌이에요.
I've arranged an absolutely amazing blind date.
나는 절대적으로 정리했다 놀라운 소개팅.
Just go for it once.
한 번만 가보세요.
Just do it. No questions.
그냥 하세요. 질문이 없습니다.
Dad, after what happened last time, another blind date?
아빠, 그 일이 있은 후에 저번에 또 소개팅?
I'm not doing it, really not doing it.
안 하는 편이에요, 정말 안 하는 편이에요.
Come on, you know last time doesn't count, right?
자, 저번에 알았잖아 계산되지 않죠?
This time it's not just good conditions.
이번에는 단지 좋은 조건만은 아닙니다.
Good conditions plus a really nice person.
좋은 조건에 정말 좋은 사람까지.
You know your dad has high standards for people, right?
너희 아버지가 그러셨단 거 알지? 사람들에 대한 기준이 높죠?
Enough. If you keep talking like that, I'm hanging up. I'm busy. Goodbye.
충분합니다. 계속 그런 식으로 얘기하면 전화를 끊습니다. 나는 바쁘다. 안녕히 가세요.
Ah, enough with the blind dates.
아, 소개팅은 이제 그만.
I prefer to meet people naturally.
나는 사람들을 자연스럽게 만나는 것을 더 좋아한다.
Alright.
괜찮은.
I'll find someone who likes me for me.
나 대신 나를 좋아해주는 사람을 찾아보겠습니다.
Is something going on between those two?
두 사람 사이에 무슨 일이 벌어지고 있는 걸까요?
Her late husband, that would be the President's brother?
그녀의 죽은 남편은 대통령의 동생?
But what does that have to do with the hand-holding?
그런데 그게 무슨 상관이 있는 걸까요? 손을 잡고?
Wow, I...
와, 나...
I truly never imagined you two were family.
너희 둘이 가족일 거라고는 정말 상상도 못 했어.
So that means she's Se Hyeon's mom?
그렇다면 그 사람이 세현의 엄마라는 뜻인가요?
Ah, what a small world.
아, 정말 작은 세상이군요.
Now that you mention it they do resemble each other a bit.
이제 그걸 언급하니까 그들은 서로 조금 비슷합니다.
President.
대통령.
- Yes? - Are you okay?
- 예? - 괜찮으세요?
What? I'm fine.
무엇? 잘 지내요.
Eat quickly, it's getting cold.
빨리 드세요, 추워요.
Yes.
예.
So when did you first meet my sister-in-law?
그럼 내 처제를 언제 처음 만났나요?
The first time?
처음으로?
Uh...
어...
Well...
음...
Ah! That day.
아! 그날.
The day I confirmed my pregnancy at that hospital.
임신 사실을 확인한 날 그 병원에서.
Then how many times have you met?
그럼 몇 번 만났어요?
When and where?
언제, 어디서?
Why are you asking?
왜 묻는거야?
Just curious.
그냥 궁금해서요.
Don't overthink it, just eat.
너무 생각하지 말고 그냥 먹어보세요.
The date ended so quick.
데이트가 너무 빨리 끝났어요.
What's your purpose in approaching Jang Hui Won?
당신의 목적은 무엇입니까 장희원에게 접근?
Didn't I already say I'd give Taehan Group to Se Hyeon?
내가 이미 주겠다고 말하지 않았나요? 대한그룹이 세현에게?
Purpose?
목적?
I already said it was a coincidence earlier.
아까도 우연이었다고 했잖아.
If you touch Jang Hui Won, I won't hold back anymore.
장희원을 만지면 더 이상 참지 않겠습니다.
Is that how someone who promised Taehan Group behaves?
약속한 사람이 그런 걸까 대한그룹은 행동하는가?
You're still acting like this.
당신은 아직도 이런 식으로 행동하고 있습니다.
How can I trust you?
내가 어떻게 당신을 믿을 수 있나요?
Do you still blame me for my brother's death?
아직도 내 동생의 죽음에 대해 나를 비난합니까?
Because of the guilt I felt, I've lived the way you wanted.
내가 느꼈던 죄책감 때문에, 나는 당신이 원하는 대로 살아왔습니다.
I just did the basics without greed, taking over what my brother wanted to do.
욕심없이 기본만 했고, 형이 하고 싶었던 일을 이어받는 것.
Even so, what are you so afraid of?
그럼에도 불구하고 당신은 무엇을 그렇게 두려워합니까?
You were the one who crossed the line.
선을 넘은 것은 당신이었습니다.
Now I'll protect my loved ones too.
이제 사랑하는 사람도 내가 지켜줄게요.
I'm curious.
나는 궁금하다.
I'll be looking forward to it.
나는 그것을 기대하고 있을 것이다.
You'll have to do your best to protect them.
그들을 보호하기 위해 최선을 다해야 합니다.
Oh, Professor Lee, nice to see you.
아, 이교수님, 반갑습니다.
Professor Lee, why is it so hard to have one meal together?
이교수님, 왜 이렇게 힘드세요? 한 끼 같이 먹을까?
- Well... - Let's meet more often.
- 음... - 더 자주 만나자.
We're not going to put up walls just because you're a lecturer.
우리는 벽을 세우지 않을 거예요 단지 당신이 강사이기 때문이에요.
Yes.
예.
Well, my eldest son is getting married this time.
글쎄, 내 큰 아들 이번에 결혼한다.
So I wanted to treat you to a meal.
그래서 나는 당신에게 식사를 대접하고 싶었습니다.
Make some time.
시간을 좀 내세요.
Oh, Professor, congratulations.
아 교수님, 축하드립니다.
People these days aren't getting married much.
요즘 사람들은 결혼을 많이 안 해요.
Exactly.
정확히.
We've been worried about non-marriage and stuff,
우리는 걱정했어요 비혼 등등
and now he's finally getting married.
그리고 이제 그는 마침내 결혼을 하게 되었습니다.
Not marrying is a problem,
결혼 안한게 문제지
but meeting people and breaking up too easily is also a big issue.
하지만 사람을 만나고 헤어지는 건 너무 쉽게 하는 것도 큰 문제다.
They divorce like it's nothing.
그들은 아무 일도 아닌 것처럼 이혼합니다.
And what about those who have shotgun weddings?
그리고 그것들은 어떻습니까? 누가 산탄총 결혼식을 합니까?
These days, they don't even consider that a big deal.
요즘은 심지어 그렇지도 않지 그건 큰 일이라고 생각해.
What is the world coming to?
세상은 어떻게 될까요?
We need to keep a close eye on the kids.
우리는 아이들을 주의 깊게 관찰해야 합니다.
But is that really that bad?
하지만 그게 정말 그렇게 나쁜 걸까요?
If they don't take responsibility, then yes.
책임을 지지 않는다면 그렇습니다.
That's right, but...
그렇긴 한데...
Whether it's shotgun weddings or divorce, they're paths people choose.
엽기결혼이든 이혼이든 그것은 사람들이 선택하는 길이다.
Having others judge that recklessly feels
함부로 느끼는 것을 다른 사람이 판단하게 하는 것
not right, I think.
내 생각엔 옳지 않은 것 같아.
Well, Professor Lee has a point.
글쎄요, 이 교수의 주장에는 일리가 있습니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Professor, I'm really looking forward to it.
교수님, 정말 기대됩니다.
Where are we going this time?
이번에는 어디로 갈까요?
Seriously, just looking at the steak, and now ramyeon?
진심 스테이크만 봐도 그럼 이제 라면?
I don't think he even got to eat much.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 많이 먹을 필요도 없을 것 같아.
[President Kang Du Jun]
[강두준 회장]
Yes, President.
네, 대통령님.
- What are you doing? - Well...
- 뭐하세요? - 음...
[Growing Hops Malts] Rea... reading.
[홉 몰트 성장] 정말... 읽고 있어요.
Reading?
독서?
Yes, as a hobby.
응, 취미로.
When I find parts I like while reading, I scrapbook them.
책을 읽다가 마음에 드는 부분을 발견하면, 나는 그것들을 스크랩북한다.
Anyway, sorry for sending you home so suddenly.
아무튼 미안해 갑자기 집에 보내주네.
Something urgent came up.
급한 일이 생겼습니다.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
괜찮아요. 걱정하지 마세요.
I just felt bad, that's why.
그냥 기분이 나빠서 그랬어요.
It was our first date since we started dating.
우리의 첫 데이트였어 우리가 데이트를 시작한 이후로.
President, are you the type to read too much into things like that?
대통령님, 당신은 글을 읽는 타입이신가요? 그런 일에 너무 빠져 있나요?
Absolutely, I really read too much into things.
물론, 정말 읽었습니다. 일에 너무 많은 것을요.
So let's just void this one.
그러니 이것을 무효화합시다.
- Void? - Just name anywhere you want to go.
- 무효의? - 가고 싶은 곳의 이름만 말하면 됩니다.
I'll prepare properly next time.
다음에는 제대로 준비하겠습니다.
You mean
당신 말은
anywhere?
어디든?
Hurry up!
서둘러요!
- No, this place is... - Quickly.
- 아니, 이곳은... - 빨리.
I said hurry up.
나는 서둘러라고 말했다.
Ta-da!
짜잔!
I told you to pick wherever you want, but why an amusement park?
원하는 곳을 선택하라고 했는데, 그런데 왜 놀이공원이야?
You probably can't even ride properly.
아마 제대로 타지도 못할 겁니다.
I only come here for the churros, you know?
난 츄러스 먹으러 여기 오는 거 알지?
No time. Let's go, quick.
시간이 없습니다. 가자, 빨리.
- Quick, quick! - Why eat churros here?
- 빨리, 빨리! - 왜 여기서 츄러스를 먹나요?
Hey!
여기요!
I don't wear headbands like this.
저는 이런 머리띠는 안해요.
This one, this one.
이것, 이것.
This is better.
이것이 더 좋습니다.
But isn't this so exciting?
그런데 이게 너무 흥미롭지 않나요?
The weather's perfect too.
날씨도 완벽해요.
Do you like it that much?
그렇게 좋아해요?
Yes.
예.
Crazy.
미친.
You really can't ride that.
당신은 정말 그것을 탈 수 없습니다.
I know. Who even rides that?
알아요. 누가 그런 걸 타나요?
Wow.
우와.
Then I'll take this one.
그럼 이건 내가 가져갈게.
Why am I riding this?
내가 이걸 왜 타고 있는 걸까?
President! President!
대통령! 대통령!
Look here!
여기 보세요!
President!
대통령!
Look here, over here!
여기 좀 보세요, 여기요!
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- Yum. - Is it delicious?
- 냠. - 맛있나요?
Yes.
예.
Slow down, you'll get indigestion.
천천히 하세요, 소화불량에 걸릴 거예요.
You got it all over your lips.
입술 전체에 묻었어요.
Wow, there's something really pretty over there.
와, 뭔가 있다 거기 정말 예뻐요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
- I don't have to ride. - It's fun to ride together.
- 탈 필요 없어요. - 같이 타면 재미있어요.
This is actually my first time on a carousel.
사실 회전목마는 이번이 처음이에요.
I never went to amusement parks with my family as a kid.
나는 놀이공원에 가본 적이 없다. 어렸을 때 가족과 함께.
Later with friends, I mostly rode extreme rides.
나중에 친구들이랑 저는 주로 익스트림 라이드를 탔습니다.
Ah, thanks to our Yeol Mu, I finally get to ride this.
아 우리 열무 덕분에 드디어 이걸 타게 됐네요.
Wow, this is fun.
와, 이거 재미있네요.
Why are you waving your hand?
왜 손을 흔들고 있나요?
It's customary to wave when you're on a carousel.
손을 흔드는 것이 습관이다 회전목마에 있을 때요.
People take pictures, you know.
사람들은 사진을 찍습니다.
Get off carefully.
조심히 내리세요.
Why won't you hold my hand?
왜 내 손을 잡지 않죠?
Oh.
오.
- Well... - Please exit safely.
- 음... - 안전하게 퇴장해주세요.
They're telling us to exit.
그들은 우리에게 나가라고 말하고 있습니다.
I've heard a lot about you from the director.
감독님한테 얘기를 많이 들었어요.
At the company, he constantly brags about you, Mi Ran.
회사에서는 끊임없이 자랑하는구나, 미란.
He says you're such a kind daughter.
그 사람은 당신이 정말 친절한 딸이라고 하더군요.
Here, use this.
여기, 이것을 사용하세요.
Yes, thank you.
네, 감사합니다.
Did my dad really say that?
우리 아빠가 정말 그렇게 말했나요?
- Yes. - That doesn't sound like him.
- 예. - 그 사람은 아닌 것 같은데.
I asked the director first
감독님께 먼저 물어봤는데
if I could meet you, Mi Ran.
만날 수 있다면, 미란.
Thank you so much for coming again.
다시 와주셔서 정말 감사드립니다.
Not at all.
별말씀을요.
Now, I too,
이제 나도,
want to meet someone who likes me.
나를 좋아하는 사람을 만나고 싶다.
Use this.
이것을 사용하십시오.
Have some cake too.
케이크도 드세요.
What? He's so considerate and sweet.
뭐? 그는 정말 사려 깊고 다정해요.
Just like Cha Min Uk.
차민욱처럼
Mi Ran, enjoy your meal.
미란 씨, 맛있게 드세요.
Mi Ran! Mi Ran!
미란! 미란!
- Mi Ran? - Yes?
- 미란? - 예?
Ah, I'm sorry. What did you say?
아, 미안해요. 뭐라고 하셨나요?
Please tell me everything you like, Mi Ran.
좋아하는 거 다 말해주세요, 미란 씨.
Favorite foods, hobbies.
좋아하는 음식, 취미.
I want to know it all.
나는 그것을 모두 알고 싶다.
What you enjoy.
당신이 즐기는 것.
Oh, me?
아, 나?
I like a lot of things.
나는 많은 것을 좋아한다.
I like shopping,
나는 쇼핑을 좋아하고,
and I love eating delicious food.
그리고 나는 맛있는 음식을 먹는 걸 좋아해요.
I'll walk you home.
집까지 데려다줄게
If that's uncomfortable, at least nearby.
그게 불편하다면 적어도 근처에는요.
No need.
필요하지 않습니다.
It looked like something urgent came up at work.
뭔가 닮았어 직장에 급한 일이 생겼다.
You should go check quickly.
빨리 확인하러 가셔야 해요.
It's not as urgent as walking you home.
집까지 걸어가는 것만큼 긴급한 일은 아닙니다.
I'm really fine.
난 정말 괜찮아요.
I'll get home quickly if I take a taxi.
택시를 타면 집에 빨리 갈 거예요.
Then let's go shopping together next time.
그럼 다음에는 같이 쇼핑 가자.
I'll definitely walk you home then.
그럼 꼭 집까지 데려다줄게.
Take care.
잘 지내세요.
Yes.
예.
He's a really good person.
그는 정말 좋은 사람이에요.
Wow, everything about him is great. But he's not Cha Min Uk.
와, 그에 관한 모든 것이 훌륭해요. 하지만 그는 차민욱이 아니다.
I guess I just like Cha Min Uk.
그냥 차민욱을 좋아하는 것 같아요.
If it's not Cha Min Uk,
차민욱이 아니면
it just doesn't work.
그것은 단지 작동하지 않습니다.
And what about those who have shotgun weddings?
그리고 그것들은 어떻습니까? 누가 산탄총 결혼식을 합니까?
These days, they don't even consider that a big deal.
요즘은 심지어 그렇지도 않지 그건 큰 일이라고 생각해.
What is the world coming to?
세상은 어떻게 될까요?
We need to keep a close eye on the kids.
우리는 아이들을 주의 깊게 관찰해야 합니다.
Jeez.
이런.
[Hui Won]
[희원]
The subscriber you are calling is not available.
전화를 걸고 있는 가입자 사용할 수 없습니다.
What could she be doing at this hour?
이 시간에 그녀는 무엇을 하고 있을까?
And she's with child.
그리고 그녀는 아이를 갖고 있어요.
[Hui Won]
[희원]
The subscriber you are calling is not available.
전화를 걸고 있는 가입자 사용할 수 없습니다.
She doesn't even realize I said that for her own good.
그녀는 깨닫지도 못해요 나는 그녀 자신의 이익을 위해 그렇게 말했습니다.
Now she won't even talk to me? What is this?
이제 그 사람은 나한테 말조차 안 하려나? 이게 뭔가요?
But your hand...
그런데 네 손이...
Aren't you tired?
피곤하지 않나요?
I'm okay.
난 괜찮아.
It was fun getting some fresh air after a while.
신선한 공기를 마시는 것이 즐거웠습니다 잠시 후.
- But President... - The food there wasn't great earlier.
- 그런데 대통령님... - 예전에는 음식이 별로였거든요.
I wanted to treat you to something delicious.
나는 당신에게 맛있는 것을 대접하고 싶었습니다.
It was fine.
괜찮았어요.
I'm getting tired now.
나는 이제 피곤해지고 있다.
I should go home and rest.
집에 가서 쉬어야겠어요.
Oh? Then get some rest now.
오? 그럼 이제 좀 쉬세요.
I'll wake you when we get there.
거기 도착하면 깨워드릴게요.
Why do you keep avoiding my hand?
왜 자꾸 내 손을 피하는 거야?
- Huh? - My hand.
- 뭐? - 내 손.
You keep avoiding it.
계속 피하고 계시네요.
- It's not... - I'm not saying this to you in a bad way.
- 그렇지 않아... - 나쁘게 말하는 것이 아닙니다.
I just don't want to get the wrong idea.
나는 단지 잘못된 생각을 갖고 싶지 않을 뿐입니다.
I need to know so I can help or understand.
도와주거나 이해하려면 알아야 합니다.
Is there a reason?
이유가 있나요?
A reason why you can't hold hands?
손을 잡지 못하는 이유?
President!
대통령!
Why aren't you answering your phone?
왜 전화를 안 받나요?
Oh, Mom.
아, 엄마.
And you said 'President'?
그런데 '대통령'이라고 했죠?
Nice to meet you. My name is Kang Du Jun.
만나서 반가워요. 내 이름은 강두준이에요.
This is the person I mentioned.
제가 언급한 사람이 바로 이 사람입니다.
Wait, so the man who got you pregnant
잠깐만요 그럼 당신을 임신하게 한 남자가
is the President at your company?
사장이 너희 회사에 있어?
I was just about to tell you.
방금 당신에게 말하려고 했어요.
What do you expect to do now?
이제 무엇을 할 것으로 예상하시나요?
Are you just playing around with an employee?
그냥 직원이랑 장난치는 거야?
Surely you're not thinking of just throwing money at this later, right?
확실히 당신은 생각하고 있지 않습니다 나중에 이것저것 돈을 버는 것 뿐이지, 그렇지?
Just because you're the President, does that make it okay?
당신이 대통령이라는 이유만으로 그거면 괜찮아?
Mother, first of all, I'm truly sorry.
어머니, 우선 정말 죄송합니다.
Don't call me that!
그렇게 부르지 마세요!
Mom, please calm down.
엄마, 진정하세요.
You're just the same.
당신도 똑같습니다.
Do you even have a plan?
혹시 계획이라도 있으신가요?
If people find out, how are you going to deal with it?
사람들이 알게 되면, 당신은 그것을 어떻게 처리할 건가요?
Is that why you said you won't get married?
그래서 결혼 안 하겠다고 한 거야?
Because it's obvious his family would oppose it?
뻔하니까 그의 가족이 반대할까요?
Why did you let things get this far, you idiot!
왜 일을 허락했나요? 여기까지 와라, 바보야!
Please stop.
그만하세요.
How far are you going to embarrass me?
나를 얼마나 당황하게 할 건가요?
You told me it's my life and to live it my way,
넌 그게 내 인생이라고 말했지 그리고 내 방식대로 살기 위해,
regret it, cry myself sick, whatever!
후회해, 아프다고 울어, 뭐든지!
You said you'd keep it no matter what.
무슨 일이 있어도 지키겠다고 했잖아.
You said you won't get married!
너 결혼 안 할 거라고 했잖아!
Then what on earth are you going to do?
그러면 도대체 무엇을 할 건가요?
Do you think raising a child alone is easy?
혼자 아이 키우는 게 쉽다고 생각하시나요?
- Is raising a child a joke? - I also...
- 아이 키우는 게 장난인가요? - 나도...
I also want to get married.
나도 결혼하고 싶어요.
Do you know why I said I wouldn't get married?
내가 왜 말했는지 아세요? 나는 결혼하지 않을 것입니까?
Do you think I don't want a normal family like everyone else?
내가 원하지 않는다고 생각하나요? 다른 사람들과 같은 평범한 가족?
It's all because of you, Mom.
다 당신 때문이에요, 엄마.
You never showed me a single day of happiness after you got married.
넌 단 하루도 나에게 보여주지 않았어 결혼 후의 행복.
How could I follow that path when I saw that?
그걸 본 내가 어떻게 그 길을 따라갈 수 있었겠는가?
I...
나는...
I completely understand your concerns.
나는 당신의 우려를 완전히 이해합니다.
I will do my utmost to protect Hui Won and the child from getting hurt.
희원이를 지키기 위해 최선을 다하겠습니다. 그리고 아이가 다치지 않게.
I'll protect them with everything I have.
나는 내가 가진 모든 것을 다해 그들을 보호할 것이다.
So,
그래서,
please trust me a little
나를 좀 믿어주세요
and watch over us.
그리고 우리를 지켜주세요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Here.
여기.
I'm sorry. This is embarrassing.
죄송합니다. 정말 당황스럽네요.
What's embarrassing?
뭐가 창피해요?
It's not your fault.
그것은 당신의 잘못이 아닙니다.
Actually, I was also
사실 나도 그랬어
born before my parents got married.
부모님이 결혼하기 전에 태어났어요.
My mom and dad
우리 엄마 아빠
really liked each other even though they were young, so that part was fine.
그래도 서로 정말 좋아했지 어려서 그런 부분은 괜찮았어요.
But soon after I was born, my dad started cheating constantly.
그런데 태어나자마자 아버지는 끊임없이 바람을 피우기 시작했습니다.
Because of that,
그 때문에,
my mom suffered raising me,
엄마가 나를 키우느라 고생하셨고,
and they ended up divorcing
그리고 그들은 결국 이혼했어요
before I even started elementary school.
초등학교에 입학하기도 전에요.
Now, whenever she sees me, I guess she thinks of my dad.
이제 그녀는 나를 볼 때마다 아무래도 그 사람은 우리 아빠를 생각하는 것 같아요.
Well,
글쎄,
I grew up without receiving love.
나는 사랑을 받지 못하고 자랐다.
That's why
그렇기 때문에
I didn't want to get married either,
나도 결혼하고 싶지 않았어.
and I resent my mom so much for making me this way,
그리고 난 엄마를 원망해요 나를 이렇게 만들어줘서 너무 고마워요
but I feel like such a fool because I can't bring myself to leave her.
그런데 내가 정말 바보가 된 것 같아 왜냐하면 나는 그녀를 떠날 수 없기 때문입니다.
Anyway, my mom has always been unfinished homework for me.
아무튼 우리 엄마는 늘 그래왔어 나에게 끝나지 않은 숙제.
I understand completely.
나는 완전히 이해합니다.
Everyone's got some unfinished homework in their life.
다들 좀 갖고 있어 인생에서 끝나지 않은 숙제.
And mine
그리고 내
is in my hands, my homework.
내 손에, 내 숙제가 있습니다.
Uh!
음!
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 괜찮으세요? - 응.
Han Jun, pull yourself together!
한준아, 힘내라!
Hurry, Han Jun!
서둘러라 한준아!
If this keeps up, you'll be in danger too.
계속 이러면 너도 위험해질 거야.
- Don't! - Let go.
- 하지 않다! - 놔요.
No, I can't.
아니요, 그럴 수 없습니다.
- Just let go! - I can't.
- 그냥 놔둬! - 할 수 없어요.
Du Jun.
두준.
Let go of my hand.
내 손을 놔라.
It's my last request.
내 마지막 부탁이에요.
Don't let go.
놓지 마십시오.
Don't give up, please.
포기하지 마세요.
Han Jun, no! Han Jun!
한준아, 안돼! 한준!
Han Jun!
한준!
Han Jun! Han Jun!
한준! 한준!
After that day, whenever someone touched my hand, even slightly,
그 날 이후에는 누군가가 언제라도 손으로 살짝만 만져도
my body would freeze automatically.
내 몸은 자동으로 얼어붙을 것이다.
I'm sorry. I didn't know any of that.
죄송합니다. 나는 그런 것을 전혀 몰랐습니다.
No,
아니요,
I'm the one who's sorry for all the misunderstandings.
미안한 건 나야 모든 오해.
Everyone has different circumstances,
사람마다 처한 상황이 다르지만
even if size or weight is different.
크기나 무게가 달라도 말이죠.
So, you don't need to make yourself small.
그러므로 자신을 작게 만들 필요는 없습니다.
Don't apologize either, okay?
사과도 하지 마, 알았지?
It must have been terrifying.
정말 끔찍했을 것 같아요.
Sometimes, no matter how much you want to prevent it,
가끔은 아무리 많아도 그걸 막고 싶으시거나,
there are things beyond your control.
당신이 통제할 수 없는 것들이 있습니다.
Your brother probably knew it too.
아마 형님도 알고 계실 거예요.
How desperate you were to save him then,
그 때 그를 구하려고 얼마나 필사적이었는지,
and how much you long for him now.
그리고 지금 당신은 그를 얼마나 그리워하는지.
Thank you for making time.
시간을 내주셔서 감사합니다.
I can assume that your presence here
나는 당신이 여기에 존재한다고 추측할 수 있습니다
means we share the same intentions, right?
우리가 같은 의도를 공유한다는 뜻이죠?
Our intentions might align,
우리의 의도가 일치할 수도 있고,
but given the high risk,
하지만 위험도가 높다는 점을 고려하면
the executives deserve proper compensation.
경영진은 적절한 보상을 받을 자격이 있습니다.
Of course.
물론.
Early next year, we're launching the Taehan Hotel chain.
내년 초 런칭 예정 대한호텔 체인.
We're planning a total of five branches in Gangnam, Busan, and Jeju.
총 5개 지점을 계획하고 있습니다. 강남, 부산, 제주에서요.
If you help us out this time, you'll get a seven percent stake in each hotel.
이번에 우리를 도와주면 얻을 수 있을 거야 각 호텔의 지분은 7%입니다.
Seven percent?
7퍼센트요?
Once I give the signal, just do your part as planned.
일단 신호를 보내면, 계획대로 당신의 역할을 수행하십시오.
Shall we discuss this in private, Vice Chairman?
이 문제를 비공개로 논의해볼까요? 부회장?
Ah, shall we?
아, 그럴까요?
Big news! Big news!
빅뉴스! 빅뉴스!
Big news!
빅뉴스!
- What is it? - Haven't you all seen the Office Talk chat?
- 그게 뭐죠? - 다들 오피스톡 채팅 못 보셨나요?
Something interesting?
흥미로운 것?
Ugh, probably just someone complaining about the company again.
아, 아마 누군가가 불평하는 것 같군요 다시 회사에 대해.
No, that's not it.
아니요, 그게 아닙니다.
At our company,
우리 회사에서는
there's an employee pregnant with the President's baby!
임신한 직원이 있어요 대통령의 아기와 함께!
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
President's baby?
대통령의 아기?
No, that's just a rumor.
아니요, 그건 단지 소문일 뿐입니다.
Better make a good impression on the female employees.
좋은 인상을 주는 게 좋을 것 같아요 여직원에 대해서.
Come on, that can't be true.
어서, 그건 사실일 수가 없어요.
It can't be, right?
그럴 리가 없지, 그렇지?
[Anonymous board]
[익명게시판]
Whoa, she seduced the President?
우와, 그녀가 대통령을 유혹했다고요?
With so many eyes on her at work, she's quite bold!
그녀를 바라보는 시선이 너무 많아 직장에서는 꽤 대담해요!
More like she has two hearts?
심장이 두 개인 것 같나요?
Congrats on making your dream of a successful marriage come true!
꿈을 이룬 것을 축하합니다 성공적인 결혼이 이루어집니다!
Why blame just the employee? The President could have seduced her.
왜 직원만 비난하나요? 대통령이 그녀를 유혹할 수도 있었습니다.
No way. Gotta admit we've got literal goddesses at our company though.
말도 안 돼요. 우리가 가지고 있다는 것을 인정해야 해 하지만 우리 회사에는 말 그대로 여신이 있습니다.
Pregnant with the President's kid, promotion is basically automatic. So jealous.
대통령의 아이를 임신했습니다. 프로모션은 기본적으로 자동입니다. 정말 질투난다.
Why bother with promotion?
왜 프로모션에 신경쓰나요?
She can just quit and live off his money raising the kid.
그냥 그만두고 살아도 돼 그의 돈으로 아이를 키운다.
The wild part is
야생적인 부분은
that recliner sofa recently probably is for her?
최근에 그 리클라이너 소파 아마도 그녀를 위한 것일까요?
What? What happened?
무엇? 무슨 일이에요?
- Who was it? - No idea.
- 누구였나요? - 모르겠어요.
Office Talk is anonymous by nature.
Office Talk는 본질적으로 익명입니다.
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
I should check on Hui Won. She must be worried.
희원씨한테 확인해 봐야겠네요. 그녀는 걱정할 것입니다.
Huh? Are you kidding?
뭐? 농담하는 건가요?
Don't you realize all the employees are watching you right now?
직원들 다 모르시나요? 지금 당신을 보고 있나요?
They're all on fire,
모두 불타고 있어요.
trying to see who you talk to and who you meet.
당신이 누구와 얘기하는지 보려고 노력 중 그리고 누구를 만나는지.
I'm dying to know who it is.
나는 그것이 누구인지 알고 싶어 죽겠다.
Seriously, if it were me, I couldn't come to work.
진심으로, 만약 나라면, 나는 일하러 올 수 없었다.
Is there a way to figure out who she is?
그 사람이 누구인지 알아낼 수 있는 방법이 있나요?
Come on, I think it's just a rumor.
어서, 그냥 소문인 것 같아요.
Pregnant women can't drink, so won't she get caught pretty fast?
임산부는 술을 마시면 안 되고, 그럼 그 사람 꽤 빨리 잡히지 않을까요?
Manager Jang.
장 매니저님.
Do you have anyone in mind as suspicious?
의심스럽다고 생각하는 사람이 있나요?
Ah, well...
아, 글쎄...
I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다.
The test batch of the domestic hop ale beer is ready.
테스트 배치 국내산 홉에일 맥주가 완성되었습니다.
- Test batch? - It was made based on Manager Jang's idea,
- 테스트 배치요? - 장과장님의 아이디어를 바탕으로 제작되었으며,
so I want you to try it first.
그러니 먼저 시도해 보시길 바랍니다.
Here, have a taste.
자, 맛 좀 보세요.
Oh, Team Leader Bang! What's the occasion?
아, 방 팀장! 어떤 행사인가요?
Manager Jang?
장 과장?
If she's got a boyfriend, she could just say so.
그녀에게 남자친구가 있다면, 그녀는 그렇게 말할 수 있었습니다.
Can't you see everyone's waiting?
다들 기다리고 있는 거 안 보여?
Manager Jang.
장 매니저님.
Try it.
시도해 보세요.
Are you not drinking or...
술을 안 마시거나..
Can't you drink?
마실 수 없나요?
Well, I...
글쎄, 난...
I think I know why you can't drink.
당신이 술을 마시면 안 되는 이유를 알 것 같아요.
Manager Jang,
장 과장님,
are you pregnant?
임신했어요?
What are you doing right now?
지금 뭐하세요?
[Epilogue]
[에필로그]
But you know, when I look at you, you're really thoughtful.
그런데 알잖아, 내가 널 보면 당신은 정말 사려 깊군요.
I have always been a sensitive guy.
나는 항상 민감한 사람이었습니다.
Must have scored points with women that way.
그런 식으로 여자한테 점수를 따냈나 봐요.
Points?
전철기?
Taking good care of people and treating them like royalty is my specialty.
사람을 잘 보살피고 치료함 왕족 같은 건 내 특기야.
I used to be really popular back in the day.
제가 옛날에 정말 인기가 많았거든요.
Wow, that brings back memories.
와, 추억이 되살아나네요.
Thanks to you, I really remember now.
덕분에 이제 정말 기억이 나네요.
I see.
알겠어요.
Then yesterday must have been quite fun too.
그렇다면 어제도 꽤 즐거웠겠군요.
Yesterday? What was special about yesterday?
어제? 어제는 무슨 특별한 일이 있었나요?
Oh, noona.
아, 누나.
Huh?
뭐?
Si Hyeong.
시형.
Stop pretending you don't know and just spill it.
척하지 마세요 모르고 그냥 흘려보내요.
I'm all ready to listen.
난 들을 준비가 다 됐어요.
Not talking?
말 안 해?
About what?
무엇에 대해서?
Why are you like this? Just say it.
왜 이러세요? 그냥 말해보세요.
What is this, some new torture?
이게 뭐야, 새로운 고문이야?
Torture? If anyone heard, they'd think I'm bullying you.
고문? 누구든지 들어보면, 그 사람들은 내가 당신을 괴롭힌다고 생각할 거예요.
- You've been - Huh?
- 넌 그랬어 - 뭐?
- having - Yeah.
- 갖는 - 응.
- quite a good time
- 꽤 좋은 시간이었어
behind my back lately, haven't you?
요즘 내 뒤에서, 그렇지?
Me?
나?
Si Hyeong.
시형.
You're really not going to tell me, huh?
정말 나한테는 말 안 할 거지?
You took my car yesterday, and I even let you have it.
당신은 어제 내 차를 가져갔고, 그리고 나는 심지어 당신이 그것을 갖도록 허락했습니다.
Didn't you leave work right away yesterday?
어제 바로 퇴근하지 않았나요?
- I didn't. - What?
- 안 그랬어요. - 무엇?
If you needed a car, you should've called me.
차가 필요하면 나한테 전화했어야지.
I was at the office until late.
나는 늦게까지 사무실에 있었다.
I know, you even had late-night snacks.
야식까지 먹은 거 알아요.
Yeah, the late-night snacks were delicious.
응, 야식 맛있었어요.
How did you know?
어떻게 알았나요?
Who...
누구...
- Never mind. - Oh, you scared me.
- 신경쓰지 마세요. - 아, 겁이 났어요.
Keep doing what you were doing.
하던 일을 계속하세요.
I'll handle it myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
Jeez.
이런.
I know exactly what he's up to.
나는 그가 무엇을 하고 있는지 정확히 알고 있습니다.
What's the real reason you can't drink?
당신이 술을 마시지 못하는 진짜 이유는 무엇입니까?
Has anyone seen Manager Jang drinking recently?
장과장 본 사람 있어? 최근에 술을 마셨나요?
Pregnant?
임신한?
Then the person at the center of that rumor is...
그러면 그 사람 그 소문의 중심에는...
Taehan Liquor's President Kang Du Jun...
대한주류 강두준 회장..
Du Jun, we're in big trouble.
두준 씨, 큰 문제가 생겼어요.
There's no woman or child involved.
여자나 아이는 관여하지 않습니다.
Before you get more hurt, break up with him and run away.
더 아프기 전에, 그 사람과 헤어지고 도망가세요.
[Kang Du Jun Out!] Thousands of people's livelihoods
[강두준 아웃!] 수천명의 사람들의 생계를
- depend on your one word. - Out!
- 당신의 말 한마디에 달려있습니다. - 밖으로!
Big news!
빅뉴스!
They're holding a press conference at 3 PM today.
그들은 기자회견을 하고 있어요 오늘 오후 3시.
So, are they going to say who the woman in the rumor is?
그럼 그들이 말할까? 소문에 나오는 여자는 누구야?
From now on, there's nothing Hui Won can do.
이제부터 희원이 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없다.
How about we just pretend we don't know each other?
그냥 척하는 건 어때? 우리는 서로를 모른다?